Arhhh, really wish I packed some insect propellent.
啊…早知道就带驱虫剂来了
The mosquitoes out here on this routine recon are the size of vampire bats,
这次常规巡逻碰上的蚊子 个头都赶上吸血蝙蝠了
and they drink just about as much of blood.
而且吸血也不算少
Quite the outdoorsman, aren't you, Jack?
真是个野外生存专家啊 杰克
You wouldn't be making fun of my survival kit?
你不会是在嘲笑我的求生包吧？
Maybe.
也许吧
I may not have stinger-proof metal skin, Arcee,
我也许没有一身防叮咬的铁皮 阿尔茜
but in a pinch, I can use my multi-function pocket knife
但在紧要关头 我可以用我的多功能军刀
and magnesium fire-starter
和镁棒打火石
to cook up some freeze-dried mac and cheese.
做一些速食奶酪通心粉
You have your tools. I have mine.
你有你的办法 我有我的高招
That's odd.
有蹊跷
Ratchet's satellite scans were accurate,
救护车的卫星扫描很准确
but subterranean energon deposits don't cause this kind of surge.
但地下能量矿不可能引起这种强烈感应
What happened here?
这是怎么回事？
Crash landing.
飞船迫降
Stay behind me, low and close.
待在我身后 小心跟紧
Autobot or Decepticon?
是汽车人 还是霸天虎？
Can't tell. Wait here.
说不准 在这里等着
Ar... Arcee?
阿…阿尔茜？
Arcee, what's wrong?
阿尔茜 出什么事了？
I know who this ship belongs to.
我知道这是谁的飞船了
Arcee to base, I need a Ground Bridge ASAP.
阿尔茜呼叫基地 请尽快打开环陆桥
Wa... wait, why?
等…等等 怎么了？
Whose ship is this?
这是谁的飞船？
Base, do you read?
基地 听到了吗？
Scrap! Comlink is dead.
见鬼！通讯链失灵了
The ship's got to be transmitting a high frequency scrambling pulse.
这艘船肯定在发射高频干扰脉冲
Ar... Arcee? OK, you're kind of freaking me out here.
阿…阿尔茜？好吧 你吓着我了
Wait here.
在这里等着
Arcee?
阿尔茜？
Climb on!
上车！
Ho, OK, was that really necessary?
噢 好吧 至于这么紧张吗？
Arcee to base... scrap!
阿尔茜呼叫基地…见鬼！
Look, I've seen danger before, what's the big...?
听着 危险我见得多了 这有什么大…
Wait here, I mean it this time.
在这儿等着 我可不是开玩笑
OK, first you shut me out, now you're ditching me?
好吧 让我靠边就算了 现在又想甩了我？
I thought I was your partner.
我以为我是你的搭档呢
No, Jack, you are a kid!
不 杰克 你是个孩子！
You are only here because this was supposed to be no risk.
你能跟我来 是因为这里原本没有危险
Got it?
明白了吗？
Arcee to Delta Team, requesting rendezvous coordinates, do you copy?
阿尔茜呼叫D小队 请提供会合坐标 听到没有？
Arcee, you lost again?
阿尔茜 你又迷路了？
Your sensor-direction could use some improvement.
你的方向传感器可以大修了
So did your aim, Tailgate.
你的瞄准镜也该修了 挡板
If you tagged that sniper back at the artillery depot,
如果你在炮兵仓库干掉了那个狙击手
I wouldn't have to break rank and engage the enemy hand to hand.
我就不必脱离大部队 跟敌人近身肉搏了
From the sound of things, I'm guessing you came out ahead?
听周围的声音 你大概是打赢了吧？
Try waiting up for me this time and I'll give you the blow-by-blow.
这次你要是乖乖等着我 我就一五一十讲给你听
What's your position?
你的方位是？
About half a klik from depot due north.
仓库正北方 大约半分钟路程处（1klik＝72秒）
Think you can find it, partner?
你能找到吧 搭档？
Trust me, Tailgate. My navigation ability... Uh... Ah...
相信我 挡板 我的探路能力…
Piece of advice...
一个小建议…
make yourself comfortable.
把这里当成自己家吧
You are going to be here a while.
你得在这儿长住了
My first local...
造访以来首次出手…
Time for human kind to feel my sting.
该让人类尝尝我的毒刺了
Ar-cee, small universe.
阿尔茜 宇宙真小啊
Too small, Airachnid.
小得出奇 毒蜘蛛
You are still holding a grudge?
你还在耿耿于怀？
The war's been over for mega-cycles.
大战已经结束好几兆周期了
Tell that to the Decepticons.
这话去跟霸天虎说吧
These days I travel solo, in pursuit of my new hobby.
最近我一直孤身旅行 追求我的新兴趣
I got a look at your souvenir case.
我看过你那箱纪念品了
You mean my trophies.
我把那叫做战利品
I collect endangered species.
我收藏濒危物种
Of course, they aren't really in danger, until they meet me.
当然 他们并非真的濒危 只是因为遇到了我
And I have a slot reserved for human.
我给人类也留了一个位置
Not gonna happen.
不必了！
Arcee?
阿尔茜？
I told you to wait for me!
我说过让你等我！
Well, partners don't ditch partners.
那个 身为搭档 要同甘共苦
Get this through your head:
给我记住了：
You are not my partner, you are a liability.
你不是我的搭档 只是个累赘
I don't believe you.
我不信
I can see it in your eyes. You are afraid, Arcee,
从你的眼神能看出来 你害怕了 阿尔茜
and you're never afraid.
以前你从没怕过
You know, for an Autobot, your resilience is quite impressive.
知道吗 作为汽车人来说 你的适应力非常强
In fact, I'm guessing that no matter what I do to you,
事实上 我估计不管对你如何用刑
you'll never crack.
你都不会屈服
Am I right?
我说得对吗？
That's what I thought.
如我所料
Tailgate?
挡板？
What have you done to him?
你们对他做了什么？
Not much,
没什么
yet.
暂时的
Just tell me what I want to know,
把我想知道的东西告诉我
or, well, you're a smart bot.
否则 哦 你是个聪明人
I think you can imagine what happens to Tailgate next.
你应该能想得出 挡板会遭什么罪吧？
I don't know the attack coordinates.
我不知道攻击地点
I swear upon the Allspark, it's the truth!
我对火种源发誓 我说的是真的！
We shall see.
我们走着瞧
No, please!
不 求求你！
Tailgate!
挡板！
You are right, Jack, I am afraid,
你说得对 杰克 我怕了
of losing you.
怕失去你！
You sure have trouble hanging on to your partners, don't you?
你显然不善于和搭档相处 不是吗？
We both know what happened to Tailgate,
挡板的下场 我们都知道
but I recently picked up some Decepticon radio chatter regarding the passing of Cliffjumper.
不过 最近我偶然听到霸天虎们聊天
At some point, you really have to ask yourself, Arcee.
有时候 你真该问问你自己 阿尔茜
Is it them, or is it me?
问题到底在他们 还是在你自己？
Do you get it now, Jack?
现在你明白了 杰克？
She is not interested in me. She hunts indigenous species,
她不是冲我来的 她要猎杀本土物种
and she's on earth. That means humans. You!
在地球上 那就意味着人类 你！
Run!
快逃！
Hahahaha... And that's why I now prefer to work alone.
哈哈哈…这就是我喜欢单干的原因
It's so sad when bad things happen to those close to you.
看着你最亲近的人遭到不幸 真是太难过了
But don't get me wrong.
不过别误会
I fully intend to snuff out your spark.
我十分期待着掐灭你的火种
And believe me, I will make it hurt.
相信我 那会非常痛苦
But that won't compare to the pain you feel knowing
不过 还有一件让你痛不欲生的事情
I'm adding your human to my collection.
我要把你的人类搭档加入我的收藏
Jaaaaack!
杰克！！
That's the spirit, Jack. Play hard to get.
精神可嘉 杰克 想玩矜持是吗
I couldn't save him. I couldn't save my partner!
我救不了他 我救不了我的搭档！
Jack, I'm sorry.
杰克 对不起
I never should have looked back...
我不该畏首畏尾…
I should have... kept driving.
我应该…勇往直前
Hello, Jack.
你好啊 杰克
Who am I kidding?
别自欺欺人了
You're making this too easy, Jack,
你把难度降得太低了 杰克
and I do not enjoy being bored.
我不喜欢如此乏味
Now, where did you scamper off to?
好了 你逃到哪儿去了？
If you wanted a tour, Jack, all you had to do was ask.
如果想四处转转 杰克 跟我说就行了
Did you spot the empty space?
你看到那个空位了吗？
I hope you like it.
但愿你喜欢
It's where you'll soon hang your head.
那儿很快就要挂上你的头了
Energon.
能量
Jack?
杰克？
Jack!
杰克！
Jack.
杰克
Are you OK?
你没事吧？
Yea, of course. Survival kit!
当然没事 我有求生包！
Airachnid!
毒蜘蛛！
Uh... so much for closure.
唔…到此为止
Now Airachnid's stuck here on Earth.
现在 毒蜘蛛留在地球上了
I'm not sure that's such a good thing.
这大概不是什么好事
I'm sorry you had to face that dement today.
我…很抱歉 今天让你面对那个疯子
You were pretty fearless there, Jack.
你表现得很勇敢 杰克
Hgh... actually I was terrified.
唉 其实我很害怕
Mostly for you.
主要是怕失去你
Ratchet, requesting Ground Bridge.
救护车 请求接通环陆桥
Need to get my partner far away from any over-sized insects.
得让我的搭档离那些大虫子远点儿
Partner, Ughr?
搭档 嗯哼？
Junior partner. I can still pull rank.
小搭档 你还是得听我的